good morning my brains doing much better
than yesterday and we are here to do
coaching we are gonna do our life's
purpose and if we have time also
our period purpose a period purpose is
more like five to eight years life
purpose I think that's pretty
self-evident we if you would want to
follow along if you want to do it
yourself you there's the kit that we use
every week in the description on YouTube
as well as their worksheets for just
this week if you don't want to download
and print those worksheets it's today it
looks pretty if ever there was a one you
can just do on a piece of paper it's
this week but you won't make a list of
values so to get started make sure that
everyone oh that's I was gonna say if
you happen to be chiming in live and
would like to get actual I can coach
someone else through this process as
opposed to do it through mine let's do
eet self coaching myself I love how I
just said my brains working it is
working better than yesterday luckily I
can do this even without the ring okay
so to make sure people are in a state of
being heart centered and in their heart
not necessarily in their head we're
gonna do a exercise an exercise called
the center of Earth so follow along with
your eyes open or closed I invite you to
take a couple of deep breaths from your
diaphragm
with your feet flat on the floor imagine
that the Sun is in the center of this
planet allow the warmth from the Sun to
enter your feet slowly move up from your
toes to the top of your head
enjoy the relaxed feeling you already
you will begin coaching
all right so the tool we are using today
is your life's purpose to record each
individual's engaged in life purpose in
three ways an umbrella purpose a
lifetime purpose and a period purpose
human beings as a group have one
umbrella purpose that is to learn how to
love themselves and others more each
individual has a lifetime purpose that
which they have come to learn this
lifetime they are a student and then a
teacher of this purpose we are able to
know what that purpose is because it
manifests as a void in our childhood if
you were a nun see if you were to look
back over your lifetime chances are you
would see a different period in your
life and what you had learned what you
had to learn and offer historically an
average individual has changed their
period purpose approximately every five
to eight years we create our destiny
through the love choice when we choose
to go on the path of truly learning how
to love ourselves and others nature
automatically kicks in to join us on the
journey to make things easier for us
this happens because we are then in sync
with the true nature of the planet its
desire to be loving to be a loving
planet versus one filled with fear hate
and anger this is a quote from Tuesdays
with Maurey by Mitch Albom the culture
we have does not make people feel good
about themselves and you have to be
strong enough to say if the culture
doesn't work don't buy it so many people
walk around with meaningless life they
seem half-asleep even when they're busy
doing things they think are important
this is because they're chasing the
wrong things the way you get meaning
into life is to devote yourself to
loving others devote yourself to your
community around you and devote yourself
to creating something that gives you
purpose and meaning when we understand
our life's purpose we become more calm
more focused and happier inside
usually start with a charming our life's
purpose we'll be doing today if we have
time today we can assist it that I can
assist you myself and discover eight
hour period purpose as well if you don't
have time we can do it next session our
life's purpose comes from the biggest
void in our childhood this part of our
purpose rarely changes these voids are
missing pieces they create the values by
which we choose to live our lives we
continually seek to fill the void for
example we may have lived in a household
where communication was poor if we had
taken on that pattern of being a poor
communicator who would be the type of
person who poorly communicates to
ourselves and to others in all seven
areas of our lives and this pattern
would have created our value system
which could not be which could be to not
think that communication is important
which could leave for example just
disrespect of listening to others and or
the ability to listen effectively to our
own intuitions we're going to begin by
looking at the values chart in a moment
we need to choose three values that jump
off the page which represent the
greatest the three greatest values you
did not receive as a child these are the
values which are missing the most they
represent the void one thing I'd like to
emphasize here is that this exercise is
not meant to put blame on anyone if you
know if you already know blame is not in
vocabulary of power touching everything
we do in this work is about learning
about more about ourselves and using all
of our resources to lead happier more
peaceful and meaningful lives we believe
that everything happens for a reason and
we learn different things from the
various events in our lives the
universal law of attraction says that we
attract people places and things into
our lives to help us grow emotionally
spiritually physically and
intellectually some people will push our
buttons others will celebrate life with
us
therefore what may appear to be
unconstructive events in our lifetime
can actually be looked upon as positive
events deep learning once we become
aware of the learning we can turn the
unconstructive patterns into positive
ones I invite you now to write down the
three values that you're missing during
childhood in case you don't want to
click on me values screen for the
description on YouTube I will also hold
up the values chart which is the whole
point of we put in the description that
I don't have to but
I'm gonna try to read this backwards and
see which one's your bluff I mean oh I
don't have to read it backwards it shows
me the proper dresser they have realized
that epiphany but it's not my day this
acceptance is jumping off the page of
you acceptance consideration I'm just
gonna take it down now because I've got
one of them seems jump off of me ascetic
acceptance and consideration well try
let's jump it off of me but all right
gotta find me other one here so the
value missing you're right in it fun
paper that's also there so the three
values I was missing in my childhood
that they're jumping off the page I
don't know if this is the same every
time is acceptance consideration you
know be games won't care to keep all
other papers all right wanna write down
what three values you were missing doing
more work to do with announcer so next
besides each value write some specifics
of how this value was missing from your
childhood for example if the value was
respect you might write down that your
family rarely asks your opinion on
anything
perhaps they rarely attended your sports
games you can share you can share it
with me and also write it down oh you
can you can follow the link and come on
Cameron so what specifics was I not
getting for acceptance
I think I manifested in childhood like I
don't
so for acceptance that there is always
this piece of needing to strive to be
more that it was never fully and it was
very intertwined with Christianity in my
childhood that Jesus is the perfect one
and you are supposed to constantly be
trying to achieve that and at the same
time never actually can that you're a
born sinner you're born imperfect and to
constantly be seeking that is not
accepting the individual as they are as
God or the universe made them so that is
free and then specifics for
consideration this one is more about
being the middle child and it always
being about either my little brother or
my older sister that my needs were often
an afterthought like oh that's right we
have three kids like the younger one and
the middle one the older one and the
middle one and so little child
afterthought and then obedience it's a
value it's like they were it's about
them being obedient to me it's that
these positions in my life that require
required obedience and yet were not in
any way perfect so parents the clergy
that they know how to live your life or
to listen to them and have faith that
they like God has put them in charge of
your life so they know more than you do
and then when they fall from grace like
the whole thing shudders and so
imperfect obedience that like you're
supposed to be following beans that are
clearly imperfect
all right so then after of the values
missing
I've acceptance consideration and
obedience and next to them no one else
is able to read it but the specifics of
what I see what I leave when I read this
it's funny it's acceptance and
considerations very intimately tied
together where they're basically the
same thing but when I tease them apart
one has to do with the Christianity and
one has to do with my birth order and so
they're actually quite different even
though it's anyway that's why it was
missing okay
studying these three values their
specifics and how we do learning where'd
it go
next beside each value right some
specifics of how this value is missing
from your childhood I did that next I
invite you to write down what you've
learned from having these values missing
in your life and I'm sharing this with
you again so what was i learning from
having a lack of acceptance hmm so weird
to think that your childhood is the same
no matter when you look at this but your
adult self is different and so even if I
had the exact same three values five
years ago when I did this it's gonna
have a completely different lens now
looking back at that childhood then and
then because acceptance what I feel I
was given that so that I can learn is
the internal guide to stop comparing
myself to anyone and the internal guide
that doesn't matter whether you're the
best were the worst really it's like do
I feel I'm doing my best do I feel that
I know what's my highest self and so
learning to do the internal piece to let
you guide my life whether I find it has
value whether I find I have value and am
i enough on an internal feeling as
opposed to an external do other people
find them enough and similarly even
though they're very similar yeah
came from different areas the
consideration is the same what I'm
learning from having been the middle
child and then the afterthought is that
everyone has something to give and when
I stop comparing myself to others I can
find my my place to give like what I
have to give so again to stop compare
person everyone is worthy including me
meeting though I'm also ready and
obedience it's like to save all of them
love it
ok what did I learn from my obedience
part of my childhood is that people who
put themselves in a position of power
don't know what the is going on
anymore than the rest of us and that's
never gonna be something to I arrive at
feeling like oh good I have all the
answers now I can impart the one other
people I am 40 and I still don't feel
like an adult
he's a dull teen here it's just to put
the food on the table it's still that
obedience again my defiance disorder my
need to be should have a conversation
like in this week of like please don't
have a position on defiance disorder
like please don't do the fingers cuz I
told you not to you don't need to do the
thing just cuz I told you to but do not
have it as you're like tantrums to do
the opposite did you like her first
psychology because it costs you a lot
and so it has cost me a lot it's cost me
a lot to have no what what was i
learning from having the obedience that
i again i had to listen to the internal
internal self and what is the word like
rebellion against Authority is just the
flip sign just as broken as following
Authority just bizarre Authority if
Authority tells you to do something
you're the exact opposite cuz they told
you to it's the exact same as not doing
it cuz I don't like ya listen to
internal guy
so like all of these are about finding
which is hilarious because it can't be
that like it to be able to find your
internal self be put in a family that
has God as the absolute focus you can
never compare in fact this is part of
like my parents were split us supportive
alert split up very soon after my
childhood but they were not in the best
marriage but they were very clear that
it was like God each other us and then
when like the marriage split up it was
like wait if we're down here are you
leaving us to like it was it was like
his that's of the order it was supposed
to be like the Bible the church said God
spouse children and so that in and of
itself at her what I was bringing that
up that there was that question
afterwards of like okay well there's the
obedience part of that but is that true
no no it's not that we kind of knew that
the fact they were giving voice to that
meant that it wasn't true wait it's gone
really up there are you putting God
above you anyway so studying these three
values their specifics am i learning we
can now begin to create a life purpose
statement what do you believe you are
meant to learn and then teach this
lifetime as a result of the void from
your childhood by the way there are many
ways to be a teacher
we can teach through simple conversation
or by speaking in front of groups
writing books or being a scout leader
the statement must always contain only
positive words words like such as no
never nothing or any negative words are
to be avoided an example of a life's
purpose purpose statement is I Sally am
a student and teacher of finding peace
with it all right so I do believers go
students and teacher of finding and
following my internal guide and I have
the word uniqueness coming out like that
as part of it is he's so hilarious I
guarantee this was not my about my
purpose three four years ago but it's
from the same childhood I my unique
internal guide follow it any trustee
interesting that okay so that is my my
period purpose is so you just like I
your name I'm a student and teacher of
whatever positive aspect came from your
learning of the three values you were
missing so my three values I was missing
in my childhood that I felt jumped off
the page of you today were acceptance
consideration and obedience how I was
missing acceptance is never being
allowed to feel enough that there was
always this striving to be better to be
like Jesus yet we're all born sinners
like way to give me a task that is
absolutely impossible try to be a
perfect being and constantly know you
will never get there my value missing is
for consideration was being a middle
child and being a constant afterthought
and always like alright let's give her a
toy - oh yeah right her needs also and
my obedience missing was having both the
church and my parents and society as
like there
you're supposed to be obedient impac
obedience is one of those things that is
a good value to have from it from the
Chris she had me and honestly it'll
chocolate so well but who doesn't want
their kids to be obedient makes looks so
much easier but having that yeah that I
chose to have things that were in
control over my life so that I could get
to the point where all of these things
being born into an uber Christian family
where God was the ruling body
even when it made no sense being born
into a family right as the middle child
which is always you know the Janice the
Brady Bunch is like the one that's kind
of forgotten and left aside oh I'm gonna
put you on screen in a second we can go
through your it's a few and and so what
I'm here to learn is to follow my
internal guide and you yes that was
interesting you got the invite code
you're in you're in oh wait maybe that's
the invite code is in those descriptions
that someone else just found it you
don't want to be on Rosa you don't want
to be on screen you just want to watch
it from there I believe is that why you
put yourself back I think that was it
that was yes if you put turn on your
camera I want to come back on you can
wave at me I just won't be able to see
it from from down there I think you just
hear that
listen so now we can move on to the if
you want to follow and I think that was
you this is the same things like yeah
you found it it's in the description of
the YouTube video you get the coaching
because if you have the values that are
missing I can help you figure out the
specifics of what you weren't learning
as well as what I'm sorry the specifics
of what that looks like and then what
you were you were learning I don't know
what's going on now hello
okay I don't know what's going on there
but that's fine all right
moving on to our period purpose which is
again we working on your period purpose
this represents what could be the next
possible steps of learning the organic
computer knows what these next steps of
learning could be based on your past
experiences and the rate of learning to
determine to determine this I invite you
to walk the brain walk oh really
interesting I didn't know we were just
doing that it's in the big kid though is
the brain walk the colorful one with all
the squiggles in the brain in the center
I will show it up on the screen here I'm
a touchscreen you can follow with your
finger on there but determine I invite
you to walk the brain walk on the plane
map at the very back of your coaching
kit once you get to the center of the
brain walk close your eyes and allow
your right brain to give you words
images colors objects symbols or sounds
that represent your period purpose over
the next zero to eight years all right
let's do that so this one here I'm gonna
show it up on the screen for a bit and
then I'm gonna do it myself so if you
follow with your nan with your left hand
I believe that your middle finger of
your left hand and just follow it along
starting with the red getting to the
center allowing your subconscious to
give you images sounds feelings you can
record while you're moving into it or
once you get to the center again this is
available in the downloading it so from
Rose I can see your finger on the camera
but I can't see you once I CEO I can let
you back on if you want all right so do
this
and paper that's fun
all right so when I did mine what I got
was a bell seems to be common bellows
and elephants I get like nearly every
time and then also because any time I
get the ones that I got really get I
somewhat I push them away and then do
allow the something else to come up
because I don't want the same message
every time and what I got was a winding
forest path a fairly well manicured path
but through the force you can't see half
the head but you know you're kind of
coming back back around and it was very
clear a BC forest which is my favorite
and that reserve there's a river off to
one of the sides working on period
purpose so let's go back to those once
you get to the center of the brain walk
close your eyes and allow your right
brain to give you words images colors
objects symbols or sounds which
represent your period purpose for the
next zero to eight years okay now we get
to decode this what do you think
collectively represent to you what do
they individually or collectively
represent good question so this you know
this was the Bell horas decode this what
did you individually or collectively
mean I know what they mean you bastards
I mean that I'm here to communicate well
that's interesting what I got when I
said that also is that a bell you hear
bell ring you don't actually know what
it is it's just a warning like it's just
it's like it's gonna grab your attention
but you're not necessarily gonna know is
it the fire alarm is it your next class
is it if you don't know what that what
it means and so it's like who the bells
job isn't necessarily to get everyone
out for the fire it's to just say yes
there's a fire you do what you want to
do with it so it's about like somewhat
sounding the alarm which sounds somewhat
negative but like being the
just keep ringing just keep ringing
and as well as the like yes to keep keep
moving forward in communication
yeah I see your hand but until I see you
it's not gonna also as far is that oh
that's not the right one yeah I was
getting yours and keep moving forward
yes to keep moving forward to just keep
following that path that although I
don't know what's coming
further on there's a faith that
following a well-manicured BC for his
path is gonna lead me back to my car
it's gonna lead me back to that place in
the forest and that it's safe enough
right even though we have bears and
cougars and BC you know how to how to
carry your body and do that but having
grown up here like having grown up in
NBC or sorry you know in Canada our
forests are going to be safer for me
than following those same things when I
was in Australia because I don't have to
be in Australia to know it's very
different animals that are dangerous or
something about that where it's like
safe enough to keep moving forward and
to ring the bell see I'm trying to get
the mixer so now I get to write up an
expert for the next 0 to 8 years I
Jubilee Briscoe I'm a student and
teacher of moving forward uh what um
communicating to the best of my ability
and moving forward
no epiphanies there but it's nice nice
to get it
reiterated so now we're gonna take a
moment so again it's just we walked the
brain walk for the period purpose then
at the center I got a message from my
subconscious what it thinks is my period
purpose what I'm here to do right now
frustrating life and I think I don't
know I don't even know there wasn't a
cell for the better not my period
purpose your purpose is not to deal with
the weapons just everything else the
overarching
save-the-world purpose to anchor the
purpose in the unconscious this
anchoring will tell the unconscious that
you wish to add more purpose and meaning
into your life by more fully embracing
your purpose remember that the
unconscious is a powerful machine which
can create whatever dream we desire I
encourage you to read this these two
these two statements every day to assist
your conscious mind and stay focused on
your purpose
so my two things that we created today
are I do believe risk oh I'm a student
and teacher of finding and following my
internal guide and during that this
period purpose that I Julie Briscoe and
the student for the next 0 to 8 years I
chiefly risk oh I'm a student and
teacher of communicating to the best of
my ability and moving forward just one
foot in front of the other I don't need
to know what's around the bend it's just
like the point of being in a forest
track isn't to get somewhere it's to
truly just go on the walk to go on the
journey and enjoy nature enjoy the river
get the fresh air here are the sounds
and that to find the the beauty in in
the journey period purpose is your 0 to
8 year purpose so you have again at the
very beginning that all of humanity has
an umbrella purpose which is to love
love ourselves and others more and then
we also have a life's purpose
I believe we chose
to get into yeah if you go on camera I
will add you to the thing you don't have
to be on camera when you're on it but if
I don't see you on camera in the little
screen below I will not add you to the
to the stream people do weird things
when they're in camera
weird weird things and so till I can see
someone looks like a real human being
and is it naked they're not the
documentary and that's it's Shila
because by all means there's someone you
miss go pony this he's coming to my
periscope a few times before but finding
your period purpose so your life's
purpose is what you were put here to do
and it's generally why you chose the
childhood you had what values were
lacking in your childhood that puts you
here to be a teacher of that because
you've got to find it sorry students of
that you have to find it for yourself
and in finding it through it manifests
into the lack in your life you're then
able to teach others that if it wasn't a
lack and you just always had it you're
not going to be in the same position to
help others learn it as when you walk
through that you walk through you know
if you were someone who didn't have a
lot of friends and then learns how to
connect with people if you're someone
who didn't know how to communicate and
then learns how to communicate and
strangely I'm not said my childhood does
not feel like a time when I was a
soluble to communicate besides my normal
not being able to communicate by normal
like feeling like I was born an alien
another and then having it be anything
and then your period purpose is I think
in order to fulfill that you change your
again I can see me on the screen not you
not a person
so we'll put you up on the screen for
other people to see but I need to see
you're an actual human being so if
you're not willing to put yourself on
camera you won't be on camera okay okay
so find the
the yeah you're like I said my life's
purpose like I'm at my childhood doesn't
change so what manifests as a lack in my
childhood is going to be the same no
matter when I sit down and do this but
my reflection on it as to like I don't
think I would have five years ago or
even two years ago decided that my my my
life's purpose is to find and follow my
own unique guide so that I can teach
other people that that wasn't I wasn't
even trying to follow my own unique
guide five years ago because I was
following societies even though I I
don't think anyone else would a labeled
me as that I wasn't oh to be tested for
koban yesterday but I constantly have a
cat a coffin a sore throat so better for
all the 2020s every time I have it I'm
like oh I'm 99% sure it's not but then
it come back positive or did it come
back negative
okay is sidetracked so yes but my life's
purpose shows up as the the same lack no
matter when I look at it but my
reflection on it my ability to view it
and see it as that that lack is itself a
gift
add me one minute moment I've explained
several times unless you show me you on
camera I'm not adding you to the thing
but you're welcome to type out your
comments and delete it but I'm telling
you people are weird with my camera and
I'm not letting people on having a lot
of people who followed the thing I know
them I know them the other time so
that's the fact you added another screen
that was then like showing something on
I don't even I don't you know what you
were up to of it something in me says
not to add you unless you're on camera
so having anyone else follow it to be
able to be helped with figuring out
their period purpose or what were the
values that were missing in your
childhood and then how did those
specific values manifest in your
childhood is it lack what were the
circumstances why do you have that as
the that's the reason again same thing
just have to show yourself on screen and
then I can I can add you on your name
changed it's just about having the your
period piece is oh yeah I don't want in
you talking about the same thing again
so this during Friday's is when we
normally do the life coaching because I
took a session
I took life coaching to be a life coach
like over a decade ago and there happens
to be tools for four out of the six
three out of the six questions there's
one we've already done for relationship
with others I did that for my sister
three weeks ago
one in relationship with self for
they're very similar tools it's like
looking at what the positive and
negative characteristics in another are
here to teach you the positive nor
negative characteristics in you and what
if they here to teach you and then this
week we did peer even life purpose next
week there is one that is the brain walk
one that will need the kit it's
following this other side where they
have three four letters three four or
it's more more letters and at each each
one you get a different
image a different message from your
subconscious and then it's looking at
those what do they mean and I really
like that tool but it did I believe it's
a question that you need like you're
you're asking your subconscious an
actual question so I'm and then that
will probably be our last coaching
session on Fridays unless there are
people who are showing up and wanting to
do this um I thought this would be the
popular one and it's actually really the
unpopular I'm here every day at 8:30
Alyssa Milano so if you want to send me
an email and let me know what it is you
wanted to share on screen what was
exactly going on if you want I'm gonna
stop broadcasting right away and you're
welcome to stay in here and say it to me
and then maybe you can come another time
and share it like on on on screen and if
it is and if I was wrong and it does
happen to be something actually
pertaining to life coaching and getting
this I'm happy to do that
once we aren't on here anyway
tomorrow is the 20-minute session where
I'm gonna be talking about what I've
done to answer the five questions over
the last week and then today over on
together tech channel we have the idea
cafe on our projects I don't even
remember what exactly it is we're
discussing but something about our
projects finances I think it's marketing
how to get people on your project and
then tomorrow morning we have the
project line roundtable at 8:00 a.m.
Pacific Standard Time also on the
together check channel and and clearly
someone is special
humans humans are I don't understand why
people actually they do but I'm going to
let you on it we can have a chat I'm
gonna stop going live and I will see
those of you who are on the idea cafe
later today and tomorrow morning Thank
You teen horoscope and I'm gonna go rest
my brain for there